Guide to Danbury's Third Century Research Collection MS 058
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Janick's Research Materials, 57697
  - News-Times summary, 57860
    - Research Notes, 1881-1886, 57790 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
      May 18, 1881 Main St
      May 21, 1881
      May 25, 1881 New Centre Supply
      Jun 14, 1881 Battle of W.M. S. Peck
      Jun 22, 1881 Weldon & Peck
      Jul 6, 1881 Water question
      Jul 9, 1881 Anniversary of Peck & Weldon
      Jul 20, 1881 Fire Department
      Jul 27, 1881 Opening of N.Y. & N.E. Railroad; Brewster to Boston
      Aug 3, 1881 Letter on Water Commission
      Aug 8, 1881 Peter Robinson; Fire
      Aug 17, 1881 New Hat Factory; E.S. Benedict
      Oct 8, 1881 Annual town meeting
      Oct 21, 1881 Democratic Senate Convention
      Nov 2, 1881 High School
      Nov 8, 1881 State Election
      Nov 9, 1881 Election; Italians
      Nov 17, 1881 George E. Rider died
      Dec 23, 1881 Ives factory
      Jan 4, 1882 death of David Phillips; Merritt & Co. Hat Factory; Crofut & White Hat Factory; Abyah Knapp; Housatonic Railroad
      Jan 6, 1882 William & Wells Co.; George Hull; Luceus P. Hoyt; George Star; Roger Avenull; Samuel H. Rundle; Weldon R. White; H. T. Hoyt; Harvey S. Perk; Samuel C. Wilderman
      Jan 11, 1882 Funeral services for D.P. Nicholas
      Jan 18, 1882 Robbery; F.W. Brachers letters; Theo Clark; Largest Paper delivery
      Jan 25, 1882 Secretary Elected; E.A. Mallory & Sons Hatters; Hull & Rogers
      Feb 1, 1882 Article on Fire Alarm System; Meeting in Warden
      Feb 8, 1882 Hatters Situation; Foster Brothers; Hat factories develop; C.H. Merritt
      Feb 15, 1882 Danbury Hat Furriers Association; German-English School
      Feb 22, 1882 Foster Brothers; Hat situation
      Mar 1, 1882 Bridgeport Sheriff; Sheriff Crosby; Hat Factory; Danbury - Norwalk Railroad Line; Housing Need
      Mar 8, 1882 Edmond Tweedy; Borough Election; Hat Finishers Assoc.; James Wildman; L.P. Treadwell; Peck and Wildman; Opera House; E.P. Bennett
      Mar 15, 1882 Warden Treadwell; German Immigrant; Bekerle and Co.
      Mar 22, 1882 Tweedy Mfg. Company; Tweedy Statement; William R. White; Thomas E. Tweedy; Edmond Tweedy; Hat Finishers Association; Nicer Rules
      Mar 29, 1882 Constitution adopted by Danbury Hospital Assoc.; Theodora Tweedy
      Apr 5, 1882 German Lutherans; Methodist Church Membership
      Apr 12, 1882 Borough of Pahquioque; German Benevolent Society; Charles Pen; German Rifle Club; Captain Charles Peix
      Apr 19, 1882 D.G. Penfield; Chicago Beef
      May 3, 1882 Tweedy and Company; E.A. Mallory and Sons
      May 10, 1882 Chicago Beef; Richard Barrett shipper
      May 17, 1882 Death of Mary Bull; New Hat Company; Charles W. Murphy; Philander; C.W. and Company; S. Howitz; G. Kelly; Johnson and Company
      May 24, 1882 Rundle and White
      May 31, 1882 Barnum Circus; D.E. Loewe and Company; Tweedy Mfg. Co.
      Jun 7, 1882 Folsom
      Jun 14, 1882 Colored Peoples Picnic
      Jun 21, 1882 P. Corbett; E. Tweedy; Walsh, Fry and Co.; Danbury - Norwalk Line
      Jun 28, 1882 German Rifle Club
      Jul 5, 1882 Guiteau; Meeker Bros.; R.A. Belden and Co.
      Jul 12, 1882 Alfred Wildman; Johnson and Co.
      Jul 19, 1882 Library; E.A. Malloy
      Jul 26, 1882 James Bailey's new home; Charles Peix; Edgar Tweedy; German Family; Beckerle Hats
      Aug 2, 1882 Real Estate; Two Germans attacked by toughs on Main Street
      Aug 9, 1882 Danbury - Norwalk RR Extension; Wilson Point
      Aug 16, 1882 Hoyt and Co.; Cornelius Delaney; John McCarthy; C.E. Geoffrey; Danbury - Norwalk RR; Brookside Park
      Sep 13, 1882 Danbury Musical Society; Danbury - Norwalk RR; Pahquioque
      Sep 20, 1882 Mallory and Rundle
      Sep 27, 1882 Firemen's parade; Republican State Convention
      Oct 4, 1882 James Fleming
      Oct 18, 1882 D.E. Loewe new building
      Nov 1, 1882 Obituary E.P. Bennett
      Nov 15, 1882 Merritt doubles size of the factory; D.E. Loewe new factory; Bigelow
      Nov 22, 1882 C. H. Merritt Hat Factory destroyed by fire
      Dec 6, 1882 Wildman Building
      Dec 27, 1882 John S. Nichols; Allen Paige
      Jan 3, 1883 1882 - most buildings erected than previous years; Philanthropist letter
      Jan 10, 1883 Housing for tenant's; Hebrew Benevolent society; Harris Cohen; E. Stone; Samuel Myers; Morris Meyers; Arthur Edwards; E.A. Mallory
      Jan 17, 1883 Hat Factories; Byron Dexter
      Jan 24, 1883 C.H. Merrett; Danbury - Norwalk RR
      Jan 31, 1883 West Danbury Growth; Danbury Relief Society
      Feb 7, 1883 Lacey and Downs; Wildman and Clark; Tweedy and Co.
      Feb 14, 1883 1882 Danbury vital statistics
      Feb 21, 1883 Danbarians describe Danbury
      Feb 28, 1883 P. Robinson & Co.; Crofut Mill; Gardner and Dudley; Wildman and Clark; Ed Howe; Foster Bros.
      Mar 7, 1883 Borough Elections; C. H. Merritt; Description of North Main; Lacey and Downs; Edmund Tweedy; Danbury - Norwalk RR; Second German immigrant family moved; March of "15 Colored citizens"
      Mar 14, 1883 Byron Dexter Hat Factory; German Lutheran Church; German Rifle Club Ball; Wals, Fey, and Co.
      Mar 21, 1883 Hebrew Benevolent society
      Mar 28, 1883 Selleck Brothers
      Apr 4, 1883 German Lutheran Church; C.W. Murphy; `
      Apr 18, 1883 Hull and Rogers; Taylor and Taylor Law; Hull and Rogers; Gardner and Dudley
      Apr 25, 1883 C.W. Hat Factory
      May 2, 1883 E.S.Davis; Cigar Makers Union
      May 9, 1883 Andrew Know; Edmund Tweedy
      May 16, 1883 Circus; C.W. Murphy Hat Factory
      May 23, 1883 Alex M. White
      May 30, 1883 Wildman and Clark
      Jun 6, 1883 Edmund Tweedy; Union Hall
      Jun 13, 1883 Telephones ordered; Nichols Block; Danbury Temperance Reform Assoc.
      Jun 27, 1883 Borough Hall; Edmund Tweedy; S.C. Holley; E.S. Davis
      Jul 5, 1883 New Hat Factory; T.C. Milfred; Borough Hall; German Lutheran Church
      Jul 17, 1883 Borough Hall; German Lutheran Church; Meeting of Danbury Borough; Nichols and Howe; W.S. Webb
      Jul 18, 1883 McLean Bros.; Union Savings Bank; Lowe and Co.
      Jul 25, 1883 Borough meeting; Byron Dexter; Turner House; Jackson B. Nichols House
      Aug 1, 1883 Dexter Hat Factory; Washington and Kohanza Hook and Ladder Co.; Centre School; Turner House; Tweedy Mfg.; "Colored picnic"; German Rifle Club
      Aug 8, 1883 Town Meeting; St. Vincent de Paul; Webb and Company; Hat Finishers Assoc.; German Lutheran Young Men's Christian Assoc.
      Aug 15, 1883 Eli T. Hoyt; Dexter
      Aug 22, 1883 C.H. Merritt Hat Factory; Beckerle and Company; School of German Church
      Aug 29, 1883 A.M. White; Pine Groove Meeting
      Sep 5, 1883 William A. Beers
      Sep 12, 1883 Prohibition Reform Society; Tweedy; James Fleming; E.A. Mallory
      Sep 19, 1883 Hatters Assoc. of Finishers and Makers meeting; E.A. Malloy; Prohibition Party
      Sep 26, 1883 Temperance; Fur hat Makers Assoc.; Starr Bros.
      Oct 3, 1883 Town election
      Oct 17, 1883 Town Meeting; National Hat Makers Assoc.; Edgar Tweedy; Dr. Sophia Penfield
      Oct 24, 1883 Relief Society; Prohibitionist
      Nov 7, 1883 Election Results
      Nov 14, 1883 Temperance; W.W. Foote
      Nov 28, 1883 Hull and Rogers; A.M. White; Foster Bros.
      Dec 12, 1883 Danbury - Norwalk RR; E.A. Housman; Lutheran Church Dedication
      Dec 19, 1883 Hebrew Benevolent society; B.F. Ashley
      Jan 3, 1884 John S. Nichols
      Jan 7, 1884 Rundle and White; Liquor License; German Lutheran Church; John B. Nichols
      Jan 8, 1884 Danbury Electric; E.S.Davis; E.A. Mallory; S.C. Holley
      Jan 9, 1884 Hat Workers Society; Mutual Fire Insurance Company; E.S. Tweedy
      Jan 12, 1884 German Lutheran Church
      Jan 17, 1884 Borough Meeting; Danbury Savings Bank
      Jan 18, 1884 Hebrew Benevolent society
      Jan 19, 1884 Foster Brothers
      Jan 25, 1884 Hat Trimmers; Lowe and Co.; Nichols and Howe
      Jan 31, 1884 Town Hall
      Feb 1, 1884 Licensed Saloons
      Feb 2, 1884 Alexander Wildman; Fantom and Co.
      Feb 4, 1884 Tweedy Mfg. Company
      Feb 14, 1884 Colored Peoples Club; Opera House
      Feb 15, 1884 Polo Teams
      Feb 23, 1884 Taylor and Crawford; German Lutheran Church
      Feb 25, 1884 Mary Bull; Town Hall
      Mar 1, 1884 Citizens Caucus
      Mar 8, 1884 A.B. Hull
      Mar 13, 1884 Hebrew Purim
      Mar 14, 1884 Tweedy Mfg. Company; John Fantom; Beers; W.W. Foote
      Mar 22, 1884 Opera House Fire
      Mar 25, 1884 Foster Bros
      Apr 1, 1884 Wildman and Clark Party; Hat Finishers Association
      Apr 3, 1884 Hat Workers Association
      Apr 4, 1884 W. Seely
      Apr 14, 1884 Police
      Apr 17, 1884 Republic caucus
      Apr 18, 1884 ST Jorge
      Apr 19, 1884 John M. Green; Hoyt & Company
      Apr 21, 1884 James S. Taylor; Opera House
      Apr 24, 1884 Hat Makers Association; Byron Dexter
      Apr 25, 1884 Foster Bros
      Apr 28, 1884 Cleveland resident
      Apr 29, 1884 Hall & Rogers
      May 1, 1884 Hat Makers Association; Beltair Bros.
      May 9, 1884 Beckerle & Co.
      May 12, 1884 Hatters Convention
      May 15, 1884 Hat Finishers Convention; A.T. Hoyt
      May 16, 1884 Hat Finishers Convention; Hat Finisher Society
      May 17, 1884 Hat Finishers Society
      May 19, 1884 John W. Green
      May 22, 1884 Town hall; Thomas Fay
      Jun 3, 1884 Colored brawl; Hull & Rogers
      Jun 6, 1884 C.S. Andrews; Ed Tweedy; Danbury & Norwalk R.R.; German YMCA; L. L. Hopkins; Beckerle & Co
      Jun 7, 1884 Danbury Society meeting
      Jun 12, 1884 Colored people; B. Dexter; Theodore Benedict
      Jun 13, 1884 Tweedy & White; wedding
      Jun 16, 1884 Industrial Party
      Jun 17, 1884 Hoyt
      Jun 20, 1884 J.T. Williams; J.H. Cohen; Hull & Rogers
      Jul 3, 1884 German school
      Jul 7, 1884 I. W. Ives
      Jul 10, 1884 Green Bros; Union Savings Bank
      Jul 12, 1884 S.H. Rundle; school meeting; elections
      Jul 14, 1884 Thomas Fay; Beckerle & Co.
      Jul 15, 1884 S.C. Holley; ST. Joseph; Town meeting
      Jul 18, 1884 W.M. Foote; Housatonic R.R.; Foster Bros
      Jul 21, 1884 Opera house; Meeting of Colored
      Jul 22, 1884 E.A. Houseman
      Jul 23, 1884 H.N. Fanton; Hull & Rogers
      Jul 26, 1884 German voters
      Jul 28, 1884 New Hat Company
      Jul 29, 1884 Edmond Tweedy
      Jul 31, 1884 Ralph Baumont; Board of Children meeting; D.E. Loewe; C.H. Peix; G. Wisdisch; L. Mager; J. Horning; L. Peters; A. Ackerman
      Aug 2, 1884 George Downs
      Aug 7, 1884 Descendents of first families; Hoyts; Benedicts; Taylors; Barnum's; Gregory's; Beebe's
      Aug 8, 1884 Hatters picnic; E.A. Houseman
      Aug 12, 1884 Hatters picnic; E.A. Houseman
      Aug 14, 1884 Tweedy
      Aug 15, 1884 Beckerle & Co.
      Aug 16, 1884 Opera House; E.A. Houseman
      Aug 18, 1884 Deer Hill District
      Aug 19, 1884 School District
      Aug 21, 1884 100 Persons attend meeting
      Aug 22, 1884 C.H. Merritt and Co.; "Colored Assoc. of Danbury"
      Aug 23, 1884 New School House; New School House
      Aug 25, 1884 New Factory
      Aug 27, 1884 2nd Voting District
      Aug 28, 1884 German American Citizen Club; Turner House; Dexter's Hat Factory
      Aug 29, 1884 Deer Hill District
      Sep 1, 1884 W.A. and A.M. White
      Sep 2, 1884 Garfield Statue; New Opera House; D.E. Loewe
      Sep 4, 1884 Lowe and Co.; C.S. Andrews; Electricity
      Sep 6, 1884 Hull and Rogers; Opera House; Nichols and Howe
      Sep 8, 1884 Mr. and Mrs. Edmund Tweedy
      Sep 12, 1884 German American Citizen Club
      Sep 13, 1884 Republican Delegates; J.C. Burlough
      Sep 15, 1884 German Lutheran Church; F. Olmstead
      Sep 16, 1884 Danbury - Norwalk RR; Wildman and Clark; Wooster House
      Sep 18, 1884 Prohibition Party
      Sep 20, 1884 Republican Presidential Campaign Rally
      Sep 23, 1884 W.O. Hoyt
      Sep 25, 1884 Danbury Voters
      Sep 26, 1884 Library Place
      Sep 27, 1884 E.S. Davis; German American Citizens Club
      Sep 28, 1884 Main Street; Flagging (paving); Wooster Home
      Oct 2, 1884 Children's House
      Oct 3, 1884 Fred Green; German Society
      Oct 4, 1884 School District
      Oct 7, 1884 Town Elections
      Oct 10, 1884 Fair
      Oct 21, 1884 Kohanza Hose Company; D.E. Loewe; Political Clubs Organized; Peter Berad; Cleveland Reelect Open House
      Oct 25, 1884 Danbury Republican Parade
      Oct 26, 1884 E.A. Houseman
      Oct 28, 1884 Letter to build sewer; D.E. Loewe
      Oct 30, 1884 Henry Ward Beebe; Prohibition Party
      Nov 1, 1884 Danbury and Norwalk RR; Housatonic RR; New York and New England RR; Brookfield Junction
      Nov 3, 1884 Danbury Relief Society; Beebe
      Nov 4, 1884 Election sparks great excitement
      Nov 5, 1884 Final Election vote
      Nov 6, 1884 B. Dexter
      Nov 7, 1884 Alfred Wildman; Samuel Gregory
      Nov 11, 1884 Parade and Celebration
      Nov 15, 1884 C.S. Andrews
      Nov 17, 1884 I.W. Ives; w.w. Foote; Loewe and Company
      Nov 18, 1884 W.W. Sunderland; I.W. Ives
      Nov 20, 1884 Fay House
      Nov 21, 1884 Dispute about sewer; Deer Hill School
      Nov 22, 1884 Licenses from County Commissioner
      Nov 25, 1884 Telephones installed
      Nov 28, 1884 W.A. and A.M White
      Dec 2, 1884 E.A. Mallory
      Dec 9, 1884 B. Dexters; S. Norwalk unemployed seeking work in Danbury; E.A. Houseman; African Methodist
      Dec 12, 1884 German Citizens Club
      Dec 13, 1884 E.S. Wildman
      Dec 16, 1884 W.W. Foote; Rundle and White; New Hat Company; Comstock; David Knapp; Washington Hook and Ladder
      Dec 18, 1884 Danbury Housing Boom; Independent German Citizens Club
      Dec 20, 1884 Etta Penfields Private School
      Dec, 1885 Summary of 1885, single typed page
      Jan 2, 1885 Norwalk Hatters in Danbury; John Holmes; Tweedy; Hat Shipments
      Jan 5, 1885 Street Conditions; German Lutheran Church
      Jan 15, 1885 Foster Brothers; Merritt Hat Factory Calico Library; Girls at Merritt Hats
      Jan 17, 1885 1st Congregational Church
      Jan 19, 1885 Saengerbund Society; Connecticut Indian Association; School Board
      Jan 20, 1885 Danbury and Norwalk RR
      Jan 22, 1885 E.A. Houseman; S. Norwalk
      Jan 24, 1885 Law & Order League; Tweedy & Scott
      Jan 26, 1885 Police
      Jan 27, 1885 Saengerbund Society
      Jan 30, 1885 C.W. Bennett; Hat Finishers Association
      Feb 2, 1885 Dr. Adam; Danbury Hospital Organization; Danbury Hatters
      Feb 5, 1885 Danbury Relief Society
      Feb 7, 1885 Deloughery; McHerney; Danbury and Norwalk RR; C.W. Murphy; Hat Shop burned
      Feb 9, 1885 E.A. Houseman; F.E. Hartwell
      Feb 12, 1885 German Citizen Society; A. Bennett
      Feb 14, 1885 Gardner & Dudley; D. Mack
      Feb 16, 1885 German Barrel Society
      Feb 23, 1885 Truman Fox
      Feb 24, 1885 R.R.R. Club; Green Hat Shop
      Mar 2, 1885 Danbury & Bethel Railway; John Fanton; Nathaniel Selleck; Oliver S.; Michael McPhelemy; George Shepard; C.H. Merritt
      Mar 3, 1885 Meeting of Low & Order League; Board of Trustees; Danbury Hospital
      Mar 6, 1885 Purim
      Mar 7, 1885 D.E. Loewe
      Mar 9, 1885 A. Hoyt
      Mar 10, 1885 Hull and Rogers; South Carolina; Law & Order Society; E.S. Davis; Edward Tweedy; Foster Brothers
      Mar 12, 1885 Beckerle Factory
      Mar 27, 1885 Dr. E.A. Adams; Davis D. Knapp; Mrs. O. P. Tweedy; Thaddeus H.; Fire Dept.
      Mar 30, 1885 German Lutheran Church
      Apr 1, 1885 H.N. Fanton; W. Mansfield; W
      Apr 4, 1885 D.E. Loewe; Sewers; New City Hall
      Apr 6, 1885 Town Committee
      Apr 7, 1885 Borough Meeting; Sewers; Foster Bros
      Apr 9, 1885 Centre School District
      Apr 10, 1885 Peter Rowan; Mrs. G.E. Andrews
      Apr 11, 1885 John W. Green; L.P. Treadwell
      Apr 13, 1885 German Lutheran Church; C.H. Piex; Colored
      Apr 14, 1885 Sewer Plan; Turner House
      Apr 15, 1885 Foster Brothers; Joel Foster; Jones Porter
      Apr 17, 1885 S. Norwalk Hatters
      Apr 20, 1885 Gypsies
      Apr 27, 1885 Hospital building; hat factories
      Apr 28, 1885 Joel Foster; Thomas Fay; Ed Burche
      May 4, 1885 Colored persons
      May 5, 1885 Mrs. Hill; E.C. Cole
      May 7, 1885 I.W. Ives
      May 8, 1885 Germans; Rundle & White
      May 9, 1885 T. Taylor
      May 12, 1885 Judd; Susan Weldon; O.R. Tweedy; A. Bennett; Dr. Adams; C.S. Andrews
      May 15, 1885 L.A. Frerlwell
      May 19, 1885 City Hall
      May 26, 1885 Robert McLean; telephone b/w Danbury and Norwalk
      May 28, 1885 Meeting of Sewage Committee
      Jun 1, 1885 Dr. Snow; South Beers lot; Frank Barnum; R.A. Beldon Co.; Beldon; Henry Hoyt; J.A. Noble; Terrace Place
      Jun 2, 1885 Electric lighting; J.M. Ives
      Jun 3, 1885 Danbury Machine Co.; D.E. Loewe
      Jun 5, 1885 Sewage; Still River; Electrical Poles; R.A. Beldon
      Jun 6, 1885 Elm trees dying
      Jun 8, 1885 Worst fire; Beckerle Hat Factory; Beckerle Hose Co.
      Jun 9, 1885 James Moore
      Jun 11, 1885 P. Rowan; George B. Sherman; James W. Porter; Foster Bros; Johnson & Co.
      Jun 12, 1885 W.W. Sunderland
      Jun 13, 1885 Fire company
      Jun 15, 1885 ST. Peters Parish; Hat companies donations; survivors
      Jun 16, 1885 Beckerle
      Jun 18, 1885 Electrical wires; Danbury Directory (W.S. Webb)
      Jun 19, 1885 ST. Peters School
      Jun 20, 1885 W.A. & A.W. White; W.W. Sunderland; Elm Trees dying
      Jun 22, 1885 Bell Island; Flynt Company
      Jun 23, 1885 Beckerle hat shipments; D.E. Loewe; German Lutheran Church
      Jun 25, 1885 Beckerle
      Jun 26, 1885 Selleck & Osborne
      Jul 2, 1885 Rundle & White; City Hall; J.J. Fay; ST. Peters School; Edmond Tweedy
      Jul 6, 1885 Bell Island; Foster Bros; Mrs. J.A. Folsom
      Jul 9, 1885 City Hall; Berckle; New Hose Company
      Jul 10, 1885 Beckerle; Foster Bros
      Jul 11, 1885 City Hall
      Jul 14, 1885 A.T. Peck
      Jul 16, 1885 German Lutheran Church; R.A. Beldon Hat Factory
      Jul 17, 1885 J.M. Ives; City Hall
      Jul 18, 1885 Dexters; E.S. Davis; L.D. Brewster; H.T. Hoyt
      Jul 20, 1885 Turner House; Insurance companies; Beckerle fire
      Jul 21, 1885 John Bouton
      Jul 24, 1885 E.A. Houseman
      Jul 25, 1885 L.K. Mansfield
      Aug 3, 1885 A.T. Peck; Borough meeting; Boggs Pond; Fire; Foster Bros; Bell Island; Barnum & Starr; Timothy Foster
      Aug 4, 1885 C. Hull; Water supply
      Aug 6, 1885 L.K. Mansfield
      Aug 7, 1885 Beckerle
      Aug 10, 1885 lights; U.S. Grant; Joel Foster
      Aug 18, 1885 A.T. Peck; Water supply; Danbury Fair; Schuyler Electrical Light Company; Barnum court
      Aug 20, 1885 German Citizens Independence Club
      Aug 21, 1885 Foster Bros; Bell Island; Palliser & Co.; Dr. Bulkely
      Aug 24, 1885 Police busy; Rural Park in Danbury
      Aug 25, 1885 National Union of Hat Makers & Furriers; Borough meeting
      Aug 27, 1885 Turner Stevens; Rundle & White
      Aug 29, 1885 Davis Knapp
      Aug 31, 1885 Tweedy MFG Co.; C.H. Merritt; Sprinkler systems
      Sept 5, 1885 Foster Bros
      Sept 8, 1885 Berckle Factory; Sisters of Mercy
      Sept 11, 1885 Darius Selleck
      Sept 12, 1885 Danbury Hat Shops; Dye; Dead fish in river; Still River
      Sept 18, 1885 Hat MFG; Gang of 17 Italians
      Sept 21, 1885 Dust intolerable
      Sept 22, 1885 Electrical light; Green Bros; Clarke & Howe; Fred Olmstead; Henry Taylor; Johnson & Co.
      Sept 25, 1885 Joel Foster; Mrs. J.A. Beal
      Sept 28, 1885 P.D. Crosby
      Sept 29, 1885 Treadwell block
      Oct 1, 1885 F.C. & A.D. Trooley; History of Danbury Bank
      Oct 3, 1885 Grand Central Hotel opens; I.W. Ives
      Oct 6, 1885 Town election results
      Oct 12, 1885 Foster Bros; Treadwell block
      Oct 15, 1885 City Hall Sewer
      Oct 16, 1885 P.J. McGuire
      Oct 17, 1885 Beckerle Hose Co.
      Oct 19, 1885 School committee report
      Oct 23, 1885 W.W. Sunderland; A.W. White
      Oct 26, 1885 Darius Selleck
      Oct 27, 1885 Joel Foster; History of German Lutheran Church
      Oct 29, 1885 Hat MFG
      Oct 31, 1885 Tweedy
      Nov 2, 1885 Tweedy
      Nov 3, 1885 City Hall
      Nov 6, 1885 Fred D. Austin; J.S. Tyler; J.H. Benedict
      Nov 7, 1885 D.M. Benedict Lane; Theodore Benedict; Henry Crofut
      Nov 12, 1885 Meeting of Hat MFG
      Nov 17, 1885 Danbury Relief Society; Salvation Army Story
      Nov 19, 1885 F.C. Tooley & Co.; Tweedy; Joel Foster
      Nov 20, 1885 W.W. Sunderland; Taylor Hall
      Nov 24, 1885 C.S. Coom Co.; C.S. Coom; John Smith
      Nov 27, 1885 Henry Peters; ex-slave dead; F.S. Wildman
      Dec 3, 1885 Hat MFG Asscociation; Edmond Tweedy; Selleck & Osbourne; Darius Selleck
      Dec 5, 1885 McArthur Bros
      Dec 8, 1885 J. Foster; J. Greer
      Dec 10, 1885 J.W. Austin
      Dec 14, 1885 ST. Peters School; Schuyler Electric Company; Foster Bros; D.E. Loewe; Article on White St.
      Dec 15, 1885 Danbury Central Labor Union Organization; H. Crofut(Crofut & White)
      Dec 17, 1885 Taxable property
      Dec 18, 1885 Liquor licenses
      Dec 22, 1885 L.P. Treadwell
      Dec 29, 1885 Hat Industry MFG meeting
      Dec 31, 1885 Meeting of Journeymen; Danbury & Norwalk R.R.
      Jan 1, 1886 Hat factories closed
      Jan 2, 1886 Rundle & White
      Jan 4, 1886 C.H. Merritt; Law & Order Society; Hat Finishers Assoc.
      Jan 8, 1886 Hull and Rogers; First cash register; T.O. Roule; Ed Van Goll
      Jan 9, 1886 Savings Bank of Danbury; Union Savings Bank; L.K. Wildman; F.R. Swift
      Jan 11, 1886 Reverend Samuel Orcott; F.S. Wildman; Eli T. Hoyt; A.B. Hall; George F. Starr
      Jan 12, 1886 Central Labor Union; Officers elected; Samuel Main; Ed Van Goll; W.H. Tully; Mrs. Eva Baldwin; Green Bros; Edmund Tweedy; Charles W. Murphy; Daniel Meeker; W. Nolan; William Rowley; F.S. Wildman
      Jan 15, 1886 City Hall
      Jan 16, 1886 Meeting b/w Unions & Hat Makers; Col. George E. Warwick; Meeting of Sewage Committee; James E. Webb; L.P. Treadwell
      Jan 21, 1886 New factory of Foster Bros
      Jan 26, 1886 Central Labor Union meeting
      Jan 28, 1886 Rundle & White; R.A. Beldon & Co.
      Feb 1, 1886 Danbury Cemetery Association; F.S. Wildman; Edgar Tweedy
      Feb 4, 1886 Berckle Ball
      Feb 5, 1886 George W. Riley; Amos N. Riley; Renzo W. Robinson
      Feb 6, 1886 Party at Hat Shop
      Feb 8, 1886 Almum Judd
      Feb 12, 1886 J. Foster
      Feb 16, 1886 Borough Meeting; Sewer; Henry N. Foster
      Feb 20, 1886 Treadwell block
      Feb 25, 1886 Borough election; Isaac Ives
      Feb 26, 1886 Danbury Hospital Inc.; Edmund Tweedy; Masonic Lodge of CT
      Feb 27, 1886 Democratic Caucus; Thomas O. Rourke; Arthur W. Marshall; Seth Addis; George Foote; William Dewbell; Charles W. Murphy; citizens ticket; Prohibition Caucus & ticket; Assembly of the Nights of Labor
      Mar 1, 1886 Workingman's Ticket; William T. Mason
      Mar 2, 1886 Citizens; Workingman's; Prohibition; 4 Tickets; Election results; taxpayers
      Mar 5, 1886 H.W. Greer
      Mar 8, 1886 John Boyle O'Reilly
      Mar 11, 1886 Borough Meeting
      Mar 13, 1886 Association for Hat MFG U.S.
      Mar 19, 1886 George B. Sherman
      Mar 20, 1886 National Fur Hat MFG Association
      Mar 22, 1886 Board of Trade
      Mar 23, 1886 Charles W. Murphy
      Mar 26, 1886 Hat Finishers Association
      Apr 2, 1886 Foster Bros
      Apr 3, 1886 Hat Finishers Association; Knights of Labor
      Apr 5, 1886 Horace Marshall
      Apr 6, 1886 Elmwood Park
      Apr 8, 1886 Oliver Selleck; P.M Osborne; Clarence Stevens
      Apr 9, 1886 List of Representatives from Danbury since 1850
      Apr 13, 1886 Professor Ashburn; Daniel Benedict; S.H. Rundle
      Apr 15, 1886 Foster Bros; Bell Island
      Apr 16, 1886 Disciples Church; Meeting of Scotch
      Apr 17, 1886 Foster Bros; T.O. Donnell
      Apr 19, 1886 German Lutheran Church; Osborn Bros